AAA Arbitration in Government 5004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AAA Arbitration in Government
1983-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Arbitration Association (AAA)
5004
19 cubic feet
19 linear ft.
Testimonies, transcripts.
8189585
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5119: AAA Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal Case Files 6145 AV: AAA Audio Recording
Trade-unions. Flight attendants. United States.; Work rules. Air lines. United States.; Air lines--Flight attendants--United States.; Air line employees.; Flight attendants.; American Arbitration Association; United Air Lines, Inc.; Richardson, Marcia; Steiner, Carol
8189585
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 1-247 (Box 1)
  - Vol. 1. No. 1. File Nos. 1 to 22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 1. No. 2. File Nos. 23 to 49, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vol 1. No. 3. File Nos. 50 to 79 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 1, No. 4. File Nos. 80 to 109 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 1, No. 5. File Nos. 110 to 136 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 1. No. 6. File Nos. 137 to 156 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 1, No. 7. File Nos. 157 to 184 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 1. No. 8. File Nos. 185 to 215, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 1. No. 9. File Nos. 216 to 247, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 248-531 (Box 2)
  - Oct. 1971, Vol. 1, No. 10. File Nos. 248 to275 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Nov. 1971. Vol. 1, No. 11. File Nos. 276 to 304 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dec. 1971. Vol. 1. No. 12. File Nos. 305 to 328 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - January 1972. Vol. 2. No. 1. File Nos. 329 to 352 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - February 1972. Vol. 2. No. 2. File Nos. 353 to 378 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - March 1972. Vol. 2. No. 3. File Nos. 379 to 403 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - April 1972. Vol. 2. No. 4. File Nos. 404 to 429 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - May 1972. Vol. 2. No. 5. File Nos. 430 to 454 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - June 1972. Vol. 2. No. 6. File Nos. 455 to 478 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - July 1972. Vol. 2. No. 7. File Nos. 479 to 503 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - August 1972. Vol. 2. No. 8. File Nos. 504 to 531 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 532-814 (Box 3)
  - September 1972. Vol. 2. No. 9. File Nos. 532 to 558 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Nov. 1972. Vol. 2. No. 10. File Nos. 559 to 586 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Nov. 1972. Vol. 2. No. 11. File Nos. 587 to 612 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dec. 1972. Vol. 2, No. 12. File Nos. 613 to 641 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jan. 1973. Vol. 3. No. 1. File Nos. 642 to 667 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - March 1973. Vol. 3. No. 2. File Nos. 668 to 693 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - March 1973. Vol. 3. No. 3. File Nos. 694 to 718 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - April 1973. Vol. 3. No. 4. File Nos. 719 to 742 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - May 1973. Vol. 3. No. 5. File Nos. 743 to 765 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - June 1973. Vol. 3. No. 6. File Nos. 766 to 787 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - July 1973. Vol. 3. No. 7. File Nos. 788 to 814 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 815-1112 (Box 4)
  - August 1973. Vol. 3. No. 8. File Nos. 815 to 840 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sept. 1973. Vol. 3. No. 9. File Nos. 841 to 868 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - October 1973. Vol. 3. No. 10. File Nos. 869 to 895 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Nov. 1973. Vol. 3. No. 11. File Nos. 896 to 921 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dec. 1973. Vol. 3. No. 12. File Nos. 922 to 944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Jan. 1974. Vol. 4. No. 1. File Nos. 945 to 971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Feb. 1974. Vol. 4. No. 2. File Nos. 972 to 996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - March 1974. Vol. 4. No. 3. File Nos. 977 to 1021 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - April 1974. Vol. 4. No. 4. File Nos. 1022 to 1040 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - May 1974. Vol. 4. No. 5. File Nos. 1041 to 1059 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - June 1974. Vol. 4. No. 6. File Nos. 1060 to 1077 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - July 1974. Vol. 4. No. 7. File Nos. 1078 to 1096 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - August 1974. Vol. 4. No. 8. File Nos. 1097 to 1112 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 1113-1381 (Box 5)
  - Sept. 1974. Vol. 4. No. 9. File Nos. 1113 to 1130 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - October 1974. Vol. 4. No. 10. File Nos. 1131 to 1149 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - December 1974. Vol. 4. No. 12. File Nos. 1173 to 1191 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Jan. 1975. Vol. 5. No. 1. File Nos. 1192 to 1217 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - February 1975. Vol. 5. No. 2. File Nos. 1218 to 1240 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - March 1975. Vol. 5. No. 3. File Nos. 1241 to 1263 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - April 1975. Vol. 5. No. 4. File Nos. 1264 to 1286 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - May 1975. Vol. 5. No. 5. File Nos. 1287 to 1309 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - June 1975. Vol. 5. No. 6. File Nos. 1310 to 1334 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - July 1975. Vol. 5. No. 7. File Nos. 1335 to 1358 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - August 1975. Vol. 5. No. 8. File Nos. 1359 to 1381 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 1382-1645 (Box 6)
  - September 1975. Vol. 5. No. 9. File Nos. 1382 to 1403 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - October 1975. Vol. 5. No. 10. File Nos. 1404 to 1427 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - November 1975. Vol. 5. No. 11. File Nos. 1428 to 1449 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - December 1975. Vol. 5. No. 12. File Nos. 1450 to 1472 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jan. 1976. Vol. 6. No. 1. File Nos. 1473 to 1493 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - February 1976. Vol. 6. No. 2. File Nos. 1494 to 1515 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - March 1976. Vol. 6. No. 3. File Nos. 1516 to 1538 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - April 1976. Vol. 6. No. 4. File Nos. 1539 to 1559 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - May 1976. Vol. 6. No. 5. File Nos. 1560 to 1580 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - June 1976. Vol. 6. No. 6. File Nos. 1581 to 1602 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - July 1976. Vol. 6. No. 7. File Nos. 1603 to 1625 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Aug 1976. Vol. 6. No. 8. File Nos. 1626 to 1645 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 1646-1934 (Box 7)
  - Oct. 1976. Vol. 6. No. 10. File Nos. 1667 to 1686 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - November 1976. Vol. 6. No. 11. File Nos. 1687 to 1705 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - December 1976. Vol. 6. No. 12. File Nos. 1706 to 1724 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - January 1977. Vol. 7. No. 1. File Nos. 1725 to 1744 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - February 1977. Vol. 7. No. 2. File Nos. 1745 to 1763 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - March 1977. Vol. 7. No. 3. File Nos. 1764 to 1783 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 1784 to 1822, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 1823 to 1862, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 1863 to 1884, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 1885 to 1910, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 1911 to 1934, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 1935-2187 (Box 8)
  - Sept. 1976. Vol. 6. No. 9. File Nos. 1646 to 1666 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 1935 to 1957., 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 1958 to 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 1979 to 1997, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 1998 to 2015, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 2016 to 2034, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 2035 to 2051., 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 2052 to 2090, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 2091 to 2109, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 2110 to 2130, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 2131 to 2146, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 2147 to 2166, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 2167 to 2187, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 2188-2456 (Box 9)
  - File Nos. 2188 to 2207, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 2208 to 2227, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 2228 to 2247, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 2228 to 2247, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 2248 to 2265, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 2266 to 2282, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 2302 to 2322, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Box 9 contains no folder with files 2283 - 2301
  - File Nos. 2323 to 2344, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 2345 to 2364, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 2365 to 2383, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 2384 to 2403, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 2404 to 2422, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 2423 to 2438, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 2439 to 2456, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 2457-2737 (Box 10)
  - File Nos. 2457 to 2474, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 2475 to 2497, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 2498 to 2517, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 2518 to 2538, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 2539 to 2558, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 2559 to 2578, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 2579 to 2598, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 2599 to 2619, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 2620 to 2637, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 2638 to 2657, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 2658 to 2679, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 2680 to 2700, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 2701 to 2720, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 2721 to 2737, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 2738-2993 (Box 11)
  - File Nos. 2738 to 2754, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 2755 to 2772, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 2773 to 2791, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 2792 to 2810, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 2811 to 2829, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 2830 to 2850, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 2851 to 2869, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 2870 to 2888, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 2889 to 2905, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 2907 to 2923, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 2924 to 2940, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 2941 to 2954, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 2955 to 2975, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 2976 to 2993, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 2994-3228 (Box 12)
  - File Nos. 2994 to 3011, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 3012 to 3029, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 3030 to 3048, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 3049 to 3069 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 3070 to 3087, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 3108 to 3127, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 3088 to 3107, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 3128 to 3147, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 3148 to 3167, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 3168 to 3181, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 3182 to 3192, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 3193 to 3228 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 3229-3449 (Box 13)
  - File Nos. 3229 to 3245, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 3246 to 3261 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 3262 to 3278, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 3279 to 3294, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 3295 to 3311, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 3312 to 3327, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 3328 to 3343, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 3344 to 3356, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 3357 to 3370, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 3371 to 3383, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 3385 to 3398, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 3399 to 3413, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 3414 to 3431, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 3432 to 3449, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 3450-3618 (Box 14)
  - File Nos. 3450 to 3466, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 3467 to 3483, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 3484 to 3499, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 3500 to 3514, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 3515 to 3527, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 3528 to 3541, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 3542 to 3552, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 3553 to 3569, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 3570 to 3581, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 3582 to 3594, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 3595 to 3606, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 3607 to 3618, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 3619-3869 (Box 15)
  - File Nos. 3619 to 3631, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 3632 to 3644, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 3645 to 3656, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 3657 to 3669, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 3670 to 3681, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 3682 to 3694, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 3695 to 3706, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 3707 to 3722, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 3723 to 3735, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 3736 to 3746, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 3747 to 3760, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 3761 to 3772, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 3773 to 3785, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 3786 to 3797, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - File Nos. 3798 to 3808, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - File Nos. 3809 to 3822, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - File Nos. 3823 to 3834, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - File Nos. 3835 to 3845, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - File Nos. 3846 to 3856, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - File Nos. 3857 to 3869, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 3870-4209 (Box 16)
  - File Nos. 3870 to 3879, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 3880 to 3889, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 3890 to 3899, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 3900 to 3915, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 3916 to 3940, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 3941 to 3966, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 3967 to 3978, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 3979 to 4015, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 4109 to 4131, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Box skips/is missing 4016 through 4108
  - File Nos. 4132 to 4141, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 4142 to 4152, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 1453 to 4164, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 4165 to 4175, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 4176 to 4187, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - File Nos. 4188 to 4198, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - File Nos. 4199 to 4209, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 4222-4408 (Box 17)
  - File Nos. 4210 to 4220, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 4222 to 4233, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 4234 to 4239, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 4245 to 4257, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 4258 to 4268, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 4269 to 4279, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 4280 to 4291, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 4292 to 4304, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 4305 to 4316, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 4317 to 4328, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 4329 to 4339, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 4340 to 4351, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 4352 to 4362, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 4363 to 4374, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - File Nos. 4375 to 4386, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - File Nos. 4387 to 4397, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - File Nos. 4398 to 4408, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 4422-4606 (Box 18)
  - File Nos. 4422 to 4432, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 4433 to 4443, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 4444 to 4465, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 4457 to 4469, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - File Nos. 4470 to 4482, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - File Nos. 4483 to 4495, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - File Nos. 4496 to 4509, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - File Nos. 4510 to 4519, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - File Nos. 4520 to 4531, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - File Nos. 4532 to 4544, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - File Nos. 4545 to 4555, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - File Nos. 4556 to 4567, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - File Nos. 4569 to 4580, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - File Nos. 4581 to 4593, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - File Nos. 4594 to 4606, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - File Nos. 4594 to 4606, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Awards and Recommendations Numbers 4619-4706 (Box 19)
  - File Nos. 4619 to 4643, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - File Nos. 4644 to 4667, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - File Nos. 4668 to 4692, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - File Nos. 4693 to 4706, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)